A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5 FA440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaigns, 1956-1970; 5; 98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
  - 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign, 4
    - Aldrick, Alexander ("SAM"), 1966 (Box 66, Folder 798)
      Special assistant to Nelson A. Rockefeller memos and reports re: minority groups.
    - Bumper Stickers, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 799)
    - Constitutional Convention - Delegate Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 800)
    - Suffolk County Rally for Rockefeller - Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 801)
    - Editorial Advitising Reprints, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 802)
    - Ethnic Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 803)
    - Fuld, Stanley H. - Biographical Sketch, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 804)
    - Graphic Arts Division - Memorial, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 805)
    - Issue Ads, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 806)
    - Lanigan, Charles T., 1966 (Box 67, Folder 807)
      Campaign schedule, reports of campaign.
    - Negro and Puerto Rican Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 808)
    - Campaign Material, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 809)
      Captain's books-Forty Third Assembly District, election districts 74-77.
    - Special Activities, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 810)
      Correspondence, permit for sound truck, thank you notes.
    - Campaign Literature - General, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 811)
    - Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 812)
      Special interest campaign activities, regional literature, Citizens for the Rockefeller Team forms, "Attack on Narcotics" literature.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 813)
      AFL-CIO tour. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 814)
      Amsterdam, Cobbleskill, Shenectedy and Albany. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 815)
      Associates Bronx Rally.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 816)
      Binghampton, Bainbridge, Norwich.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 817)
      Brooklyn, Manhattan, Nassau, Suffolk, Queens, Cerebral Palsy Federation of Labor, New York Telephone.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 818)
      Bronx, Staten Island, press conference.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 819)
      Buffalo, Lowville and Watertown.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 18 (Box 67, Folder 820)
      Buffalo, Rochester, Syracuse, Albany.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 November 7 (Box 67, Folder 821)
    - Conference, 1966 October 23 (Box 67, Folder 822)
    - Contact Prints, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 823)
    - Contact Prints, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 824)
    - "Direct Line" TV Debate, 1966 November 6 (Box 68, Folder 825)
    - Election Day - Pocantico and New York City, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 826)
    - Glossies, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 827)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 828)
      Manhatten Center Rally.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 Septemter 23 (Box 68, Folder 829)
      Massena, New York.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 24 (Box 68, Folder 830)
      Metropolitan Club.
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 831)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 11 (Box 68, Folder 832)
      Nassau County and New York City.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 22 (Box 68, Folder 833)
      Nassau County.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 Septemter 21 (Box 68, Folder 834)
      New York City.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 Septemter 23 (Box 68, Folder 835)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 1 (Box 68, Folder 836)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 4 (Box 68, Folder 837)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 5 (Box 68, Folder 838)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 10 (Box 68, Folder 839)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 12 (Box 68, Folder 840)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 13 (Box 68, Folder 841)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 14 (Box 68, Folder 842)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 15 (Box 68, Folder 843)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 21 (Box 68, Folder 844)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 25 (Box 68, Folder 845)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 November 1 (Box 68, Folder 846)
      New York City towns.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 28 (Box 68, Folder 847)
      Oneonta, New York.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 20 (Box 68, Folder 848)
      Oswego and Endicott.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 29 (Box 68, Folder 849)
      Olean, Jamestown, Wellsville and Dunkirk.
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 September 19 (Box 69, Folder 850)
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 September 26 (Box 69, Folder 851)
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 October 3 (Box 69, Folder 852)
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 October 7 (Box 69, Folder 853)
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 October 9 (Box 69, Folder 854)
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 October 10 (Box 69, Folder 855)
    - Press Conference, 1966 October 29 (Box 69, Folder 856)
      Photographs. Debate with four candidates.
    - Prints, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 857)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 26 (Box 69, Folder 858)
      Putnam County.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 31 (Box 69, Folder 859)
      Rochester, Albian, North Tonawanda, Buffalo.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 27 (Box 69, Folder 860)
      Westchester County.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 17 (Box 69, Folder 861)
      Rockland County.
    - Strategy Meeting, 1966 November 5 (Box 69, Folder 862)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 October 6 (Box 69, Folder 863)
      Syracuse, Hamilton.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Upstate New York, 1966 October 26 (Box 69, Folder 864)
      Oneida, Herkimer, Cornell University, "Patchague".
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 November 3 (Box 69, Folder 865)
      Westchester.
    - Prints, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 866)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 13-June 15 (Box 69, Folder 867)
      Albany.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 19 (Box 69, Folder 868)
      Altamont Fair.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 869)
      Association for the help of Retarded Children, Bronx County Republican Committee Dinner.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 25 (Box 69, Folder 870)
      Bath, Penn Yan and Watkins Glen.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 27 (Box 69, Folder 871)
      Bear Mountain, Olana, Hudson.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 29 (Box 69, Folder 872)
      Brookwood Science Information Center dedication-Archbishop McEntegart dinner.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 2-June 3 (Box 69, Folder 873)
      Buffalo and Dresden, New York.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 4 (Box 69, Folder 874)
      Buffalo, New York City police bill signing, Saratoga.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 19 (Box 69, Folder 875)
      Camp Smith and Buffalo.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 876)
      Chemung County Fair, August 16, 1966Buffalo, August 17, 1966.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 28 (Box 69, Folder 877)
      Cooperstown and Albany.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - County Fairs and More, 1966 August 24 (Box 69, Folder 878)
      Erie County, Wyoming County and Alexander, New York.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - County Fairs, 1966 August 26 (Box 69, Folder 879)
      Dutchess and Washington.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - County Fairs, 1966 September 2 (Box 69, Folder 880)
      Columbia and Rensselaer.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 25 (Box 69, Folder 881)
      Dansville and Hornell.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 14 (Box 70, Folder 882)
      Elmira (en route), Binghamton, Elmira, Corning, Syracuse.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 23 (Box 70, Folder 883)
      Franklin County Fair, Malone, New York, Saranac Lake.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 6 (Box 70, Folder 884)
      Fort Stanwix, Jefferson County Fair, Oriskany, New York.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 7 (Box 70, Folder 885)
      Garden City, New York.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 22 (Box 70, Folder 886)
      Henrietta, Niagara Falls, Buffalo.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 22 (Box 70, Folder 887)
      Hilton Hotel, Garden City, Jamaica, Brooklyn, Jackson Heights.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 27 (Box 70, Folder 888)
      Nassau County beaches tour.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 13 (Box 70, Folder 889)
      Kingston and Catskill, New York.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 8 (Box 70, Folder 890)
      Lake George, Senaca Falls, Auburn and Rochester.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 891)
      Lake Placid, August 23 and September 16, 1966New York City, September 16, 1966.
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1966 April (Box 70, Folder 892)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Middletown, New York, 1966 August 14 (Box 70, Folder 893)
    - Margaretta (Happy) Fitler Rockefeller in London, 1966 June (Box 70, Folder 894)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted from access. Documents living Rockefeller family members
      With Nelson, Jr. and Chief Justice Earl Warren.
    - Margaretta (Happy) Fitler Rockefeller in London (Box 70, Folder 894)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 September 7 (Box 70, Folder 895)
      Nassau County, Rochester.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - New York City, 1966 May 12 (Box 70, Folder 896)
      Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - New York City, 1966 May 24 (Box 70, Folder 897)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - New York City, 1966 May 25 (Box 70, Folder 898)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - New York City, 1966 May 26-May 27 (Box 70, Folder 899)
      United Cerebral Palsy, Governor's Conference on Women.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 May 29 (Box 70, Folder 900)
      Elks convention and Baptist church. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 4 (Box 70, Folder 901)
      American Hellenic Educational Progressive Association. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 8 (Box 70, Folder 902)
      Swearing in Judge William S. Shea, Nicaraguan President Dr. Rena Schick Gutierrez, water pollution conference. Photographs.
    - Press Conference - New York City Tax Program, 1966 June 8 (Box 70, Folder 903)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 June 9 (Box 70, Folder 904)
      Opening campaign HQ, Suffolk County Breakfast, Republican State Committee Dinner. Photographs.
    - Reception for Japanese Ambassador, 1966 June 22 (Box 70, Folder 905)
    - Puerto Rico Dinner and Parade, 1966 June 25-June 26 (Box 70, Folder 906)
    - Forty Plus Employment Proclamation, 1966 July 12 (Box 70, Folder 907)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 1 (Box 70, Folder 908)
      USA Dinner, bill signings. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 3 (Box 71, Folder 909)
      Grevi, Santiogo-swearing in Narcotic Control Commission in New York City. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 8 (Box 71, Folder 910)
      Hudson River Conservation Group, barbers in New York City. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 29 (Box 71, Folder 911)
      State Narcotic Control Commission at campaign storefronts.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 30 (Box 71, Folder 912)
      Suffolk County Republican Convention (Plaza Hotel), Fiftieth Anniversary of Marine Corps Reserve, press reception.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 Saptember 17 (Box 71, Folder 913)
      Steuben Day Parade, San Gennaro Festival, New York State Office Building for Harlem. Photographs.
    - Hunter College Commencement, 1966 July 1 (Box 71, Folder 914)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller honorary degree.
    - Garden City Fund Raiser, 1966 May 23 (Box 71, Folder 915)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller "forever" out of Presidential races, with Governor George Romney and Senator Jacob Javits.
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 June 21 (Box 71, Folder 916)
      Reception, Dina Merrill.
    - Storefronts in New York City, 1966 August 9 (Box 71, Folder 917)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 August 10 (Box 71, Folder 918)
      Honeoye Falls, Ovid, Canandaigua. Photographs.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 Ausust 11 (Box 71, Folder 919)
      Glens Falls, Yates County, Seneca County and Steuben County. Photographs.
    - Coney Island Beach, 1966 August 13 (Box 71, Folder 920)
      Tour, storefront opening.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Far Rockaway and Orchard Beach, 1966 September 5 (Box 71, Folder 921)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Rochester, New York - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1966 June 23 (Box 71, Folder 922)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Saratoga Springs - Dedication of Performing Arts Center, 1966 June 16 (Box 71, Folder 923)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Speculator, Syracuse, Warrensburg, Diamond Point, 1966 August 31 (Box 71, Folder 924)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Suffolk County, 1966 September 12 (Box 71, Folder 925)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Sullivan County, 1966 September 14 (Box 71, Folder 926)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - Syracuse, 1966 September 11 (Box 71, Folder 927)
    - Campaign Tour Appearances, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 928)
      Syracuse University, LLD, June 5, 1966Buffalo and Washington, June 2, 1966.
    - Campaign Tour Appearances - West Seneca and Buffalo, 1966 August 7 (Box 71, Folder 929)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign Photographs, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 930)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign Photographs, 1966 October 27; 1966; November 7 1966 (Box 71, Folder 931)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign Photographs, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 932)
    - Anecdotes of the 1966 Campaign (Box 71, Folder 933)
      Transcript of meeting of February 29, 1968, "Meeting to Recall Anecdotes?", attended by Gilbert Robinson, Ken Hoeck, Marguerite Kilpatrick, Barbara Jones, Marty Snyder, Jim McGrath, Pete Sveena and Jim Kilpatrick.
    - Anecdotes in Response to Letter from Arthur Massalo, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 934)
    - Campaign Division - Chairman and Committees - Lists, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 935)
    - Propositions - Questions and Advertisements, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 936)
      Interalia Pure Waters Bond Act, Constitutional Convention, etc., party enrolment figure.
    - Canvasing - New York City Campaign File Contents of B. A. Ritterspoon, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 937)
    - Citizens for the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 938)
    - Civilian Review Board - New York City Policy - Strategy Meeting, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 939)
    - Comments (Staff) to Nelson A. Rockefeller on Mayor Lindsay's Position Papers and Transition Costs, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 940)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 941)
    - New York Republican State Convention - Rochester, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 942)
      Room assignments, schedule, miscellaneous correspondence (Pfeiffer), planning memo, delegates.
    - Liquor Dealers, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 943)
      Strategy and correspondence.
    - County Committee's Endorsements and "Thank You's", 1966 (Box 72, Folder 944)
    - Kings County Delegates to State Convention, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 945)
    - Campaign Director's Files, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 946)
      File contents 1-123.
    - Endorsements - Local Committees, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 947)
    - Endorsements - County Committees, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 948)
    - Endorsements - Young Republicans, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 949)
    - Finance Committee, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 950)
      File contents 265-269.
    - Governor, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 951)
      File contents 477-513.
    - Index - 1966 Campaign Archives (Box 72, Folder 952)
      pp. 232-280.
    - Jewish Press, Eugene T. Rossides, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 953)
      File contents 209-223.
    - Republican Candidates for Assembly, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 954)
    - Republican Congressional Candidates, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 955)
      Strategy memo to Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    - Constitutional Convention Delegates, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 956)
      Memos from Paul Carran to William Pfeiffer, lists.
    - New York Senator Candidates, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 957)
    - Literature, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 958)
      File contents 1312-1318, distribution of special interest literature.
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 959)
      File contents 1319-1326.
    - New York City Campaign - Gilbert Robinson, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 960)
      File contents 224-239.
    - New York City Campaign - Eugene T. Rossides, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 961)
      File contents 124-208.
    - New York Republican State Committee, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 962)
      Rules, members.
    - Photographs, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 963)
      File contents 1327-1472.
    - Campaign Platform Development, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 964)
      Republican platform recommendations, Daily News platform comparisons.
    - Public Relations and Press Division - Harry O'Donnell, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 965)
      File contents 600-1284.
    - Public Relations and Press Division, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 966)
      File contents 522-599.
    - Candidates by County Lists, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 967)
      John Walsh to William Pfieffer names.
    - Charles T. Lanigan Campaign Report and Schedules, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 968)
    - Confidential Report - "Popular Support for the Welfare States", 1966 (Box 73, Folder 969)
      Prepared by the Research Council, Inc., Princeton, New Jersey (Lloyd Free)
    - Research and Planning Division Records, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 970)
    - Scheduling Division Records - Files of Jean McKee, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 971)
    - Senior Citizens - Staff, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 972)
    - Spanish Speaking Division - Staff, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 973)
    - Speakers Bureau - Staff, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 974)
    - Special Committees - Staff, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 975)
    - Special Groups - Records, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 976)
      File contents 404-449.
    - Speech Writers - Staff, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 977)
    - State Convention - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 978)
    - Suggestions for Campaign - Preliminary Schedule for Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 979)
    - Gubernatorial Campaign Achives, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 980)
      Table of contents and introduction to "the closest thing to a perfect political campaign this domocracy has ever seen."
    - Treasurer - Financial Reports Filed with Secretary of State, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 981)
      File list only.
    - Pfeiffer, William - Biographical Material, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 982)
    - Campaign Guide - Associates of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 983)
      Mission: To reach the Jewish community. Reprints.
    - Assembly Campaign Committee Guide and Reports, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 984)
    - Campaign Guide, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 985)
      Director and staff, treasurer, budget, Women's division, communications, congressional liaosn, constitutional convention.
    - Campaign Gulide - Deputy Campaign Directors - Reports, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 986)
    - Campaign Guide, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 987)
      Field organization, communications, graphic arts, inter-group relations.
    - Campaign Guide, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 988)
      Labor, New York City campaign, New York Republican Committee, public relations, research.
    - Campaign Guide, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 989)
      Scheduling division, Senate campaign committee, senior citiizens, Spanish speaking, special committees, special writers.
    - Campaign Guide, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 990)
      Strategy committee, young New Yorkers.
    - Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 991)
    - Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 992)
      Memorabilia (removed).
    - Campaign Photographs, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 993)
    - "History and Archives" - Directory to 1966 Campaign Files by Art Massolo (Box 74, Folder 994)
      Created in 1968, 1964 directory to campaign files, introduction and table of contents.
    - "History and Archives" - Directory to 1966 Campaign Files by Art Massolo (Box 74, Folder 995)
      Campaign archives, pp. 1-101.
    - "History and Archives" - Directory to 1966 Campaign Files by Art Massolo (Box 74, Folder 996)
      Campaign archives, pp. 102-205.
    - "History and Archives" - Directory to 1966 Campaign Files by Art Massolo (Box 74, Folder 997)
      Campaign archives, pp. 206-end and index.
    - Arthur Massolo Correspondence, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 998)
      Re materials collected for campaign archives.
    - Strategy Meeting, 1966 July (Box 74, Folder 999)
    - Strategy Meeting, 1966 August (Box 74, Folder 1000)
    - Strategy Meeting, 1966 September (Box 74, Folder 1001)
    - Strategy Meeting, 1966 October (Box 74, Folder 1002)
    - Strategy Meeting, 1966 November (Box 74, Folder 1003)
  - 1970 New York Gubernatorial Campaign, 5
    - Invitations - Tapings and Luncheons, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1004)
    - Invitations - TV and Radio - Current (Pending and Accept), 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1005)
    - Invitations - Dead File, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1006)
    - TV and Radio - Scheduled Appearances, 1970 July 13; 1970-August 24 (Box 75, Folder 1007)
    - Monthly Schedules, 1970 August-October (Box 75, Folder 1008)
    - Campaign Expense Reports, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1009)
    - Personnel - Radio and TV and General, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1010)
    - Debates on TV - Confirmed (Memos, Correspondence), 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1011)
    - Miscellaneous Information from June 18, 1970, 1970 June 18 (Box 75, Folder 1012)
      Telephone numbers, personnel list, correspondence.
    - Transcripts of Debates, 1970 October-November (Box 75, Folder 1013)
      November 1, 1970, October 28, 1970, October 20, 1970, editorials.
    - Transcripts from TV, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1014)
    - Transcripts from TV, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1015)
    - Thank You Letters, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 1016)
    - TV Monitoring - Summaries of all Channels - News Reports, 1970 September 9-November 2 (Box 76, Folder 1017)
    - Radio and TV Spots - Tinker Agency, 1970 August 11-September 14 (Box 76, Folder 1018)
    - Radio and TV Spots - Tinker Agency, 1970 September 15-November 1 (Box 76, Folder 1019)
    - Bills and Invoices - Other than Expense Reports, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 1020)
    - Campaign Bills, 1970 'November 3 (Box 76, Folder 1021)
      Photographs. Equipment, advance victory speech by Nelson Rockefeller at headquarters, November 3, 1970.
    - Research and Set-up Costs, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 1022)
    - Research and Set-up Costs, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 1023)
    - Election Nights Wrap-up, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 1024)
    - 1970 Fact Sheets on Issues (Box 77, Folder 1025)
      Aging, Agriculture, Arts, Consumer Protection, Crime, Economic Growth, Federal Economic Redevelopment Programs.
    - 1970 Fact Sheets on Issues (Box 77, Folder 1026)
      Education, Environment - Water, Air, Solid Waste, Parks and Recreation, Natural Resources; Government - State Aid, Management Improvement in State government.
    - 1970 Fact Sheets on Issues (Box 77, Folder 1027)
      Government - State and Local Relations, State Government Employees, Local Government Employees, Land Acquisition; Health; Housing and Community Development, Human Rights, Labor, Mental Disability, Migrant Labor.
    - 1970 Fact Sheets on Issues (Box 77, Folder 1028)
      Narcotics, Science and Technology, Social Welfare, Transportation - New York Metropolitan area, Transportation - Traffic Safety, Veterans, Women, and Youth.
  - 1960 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 6
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1029)
      Miscellaneous states.